- Great to stay at a resort.
- mm.
Leopard...
But...
Alma, go and play.
Bye.
I don't know what it is with them today!
I think there are some butterflies in the stomach for us to travel.
Yes, I believe that.
But...
Hello!
Pussy away.
- No, but go away now, please.
- Go and play there!
Quite Spartan Kid Zone when compared to the hotel we have just lived on.
- It's been like a kid zone, the whole resort!
- Yes.
It was only a bunch of children who have pulled around and had as much fun!
Yes!
I want to take the opportunity to strike a blow to travel in the off -season.
- Yes.
- How nice isn't that?
There is no congestion, neither in restaurants nor on sun loungers or anything like that.
Everything goes very smoothly.
But there are still lots of children for the kids to play with, and good things to do.
Yes.
And the beach was ...
- Some days it was almost empty!
- Yes.
That's right.
There we have him ...
- Hello!
- Hello Hello!
What is it, the old man?
I get scared.
Come, take my hand.
Tell me, why are you scared?
The aircraft will probably crash.
No, no, no ... it's just raining outside, it's nothing dangerous.
They can land anyway.
- They will land on the sea now.
- No, we will land at the airport.
Yes...
- If we don't land on sea ... - no ...
- If we land on the sea we will go on a boat instead ... - No, Harry ...
- Should we go in and check out the townhouse?
- Yes!
We rent this from a family living abroad.
Wow!
Oh!
Great!
You can put on Netflix, in addition!
There is an upstairs!
Yes, but we have to check the kitchen and the patio first, then we go up and then check.
I stay here.
Here we can sit and eat.
Here we can cook our food.
Here is our upstairs!
Here's my room!
- Do you take this?
- Yes, I'll take this.
I pax it.
Here Harry can sleep.
- Should Harry have such a big bed?
- Yep!
The toilet.